[unsettling music playing]
[duke] Did you actually believe you could
make it this far on your own?
[metallic clang]
[loud beeping]
I am the only person in this world
who can cross that line and walk in here.
Any idea what would happen if this machine
wasn't currently scanning my iris?
I suppose that
it would be something dramatic.
[unsettling music dies down]
Yes, you're correct.
If the machine
hadn't confirmed my identity,
within ten seconds
of setting foot inside the vault,
methane gas would be pushed
through these vents. And then?
A spark, I presume?
Yes. And this entire area
would be transformed
into a raging ring of fire,
inspired by the Divine Comedy
and the third ring of the seventh circle
of the Inferno of Dante Alighieri.
So, unless by chance,
a Marvel superhero appears,
immune to fire
and equipped with my own eyes,
well, then, I guarantee
that no one shall ever find
their way to this door.
Behold this masterpiece.
Devoid of any handles,
devoid of any locks.
Not even a hydraulics system.
A mysterious, impenetrable work of art.
What do you think?
Magnificent.
[glasses clink]
- [Keila panting]
- [Damián] Keila!
[pounding on door]
[Damián] Keila, are you there?
Keila!
What?
I knew I was right.
I knew it!
- What man?
- He's got a huge barbecue.
It's a trap
big enough to roast an elephant!
And it's absolutely impossible
to get inside.
He's a genius.
He's a fucking master. He's--
Sorry, the wine. The wine.
- It'll stain the sheets.
- Damián, Damián.
- With salt and water, it'll come out.
- It's okay.
[flamenco-inspired theme music playing]
[music fades]
[Berlin] The lady will be leaving Kraków
at 8:15 a.m.,
locked in a case on a regular flight.
The painting will be protected
by a wooden frame and reinforced glass,
which is standard practice
when lending works.
Thanks. From Czartoryski.
We'll come back to that later.
- Arrival time?
- Arriving at 12:30, Seville airport.
Once landed, it will be picked up
by a private security company.
- Mm-hmm.
- One that specializes in works of art.
Here's what I found.
And like all security trucks
carrying valuables,
it will be armored.
The name of the company is Blindesart,
and they use these types of trucks.
As you can see,
these are fortresses on wheels,
and that's where our problems begin.
No. That's easy.
We ambush them on the tarmac.
Mm? We stop them,
and we blow out the windows.
[imitates machine gun]
We grab the security guards,
and in two seconds, we open the truck.
[chuckles] Not a bad idea.
However, there are details you left out.
First and foremost, the truck's windows
are made of hardened glass.
Secondly, contrary to other vehicles,
these drivers do not have access
to the painting that they're carrying.
- Really?
- Nope. In fact, there are no keys.
These vans only use codes.
And to improve security,
these are kept secret.
And what if we use
the Russian tactic of Matryoshka?
- Uh-huh. And what is that?
- You've never heard of it?
- Mm-mm.
- From the Furious movie.
- From the Furious movie?
- Yeah.
We steal the truck
and put it inside a bigger truck.
Good idea. But to do that,
we'd need control of the steering wheel.
Why do you keep being so picky
on the details?
It's a false robbery,
and it's just to dupe the duke.
No, Candela. The plan has to be perfect,
and has to be real.
We have to impress this pompous idiot.
And the more difficult the plan we create,
the more brilliant it appears.
- Wow.
- [chuckles]
- You speak so beautifully, so classy.
- [laughs]
It's a pity I'm somewhat disappointed
we won't be stealing it.
- And why is that?
- Well, I'm a little pissed.
Our first job as a couple
isn't a real job.
But our plan is gonna be beautiful, right?
- [sighs]
- Mm.
[phone vibrating]
And once again,
no rest for the wicked, I see.
- Mm.
- You know what? I'm starving.
It's time for some fried eggs
at Pepe's place. Okay?
You stay put and chat with the gang.
See you later.
[call connects]
- Yes.
- I couldn't call you earlier.
But you'll never believe what happened.
We just left the port,
escorted by the coast guard.
[intense music playing]
As the yacht was about to leave,
cars pulled up,
carrying diplomats and VIPs.
[indistinct chatter]
[Cameron] I think they were there
to pay their respects to dignitaries.
You know what's going on?
If the Nigerian
bags of rice contain anything illegal,
then no one will check them.
Exactly.
A list of passengers containing diplomats
is the perfect way
to avoid any customs searches.
Have you found out
where they're hiding the bags of rice?
No, I've looked everywhere.
I couldn't find anything.
Nothing at all.
There must be some kind of hidden hold
or secret compartment on the boat.
The goods are definitely here somewhere.
I measured the height of the two levels.
The height of the cargo hold
and the engine room.
If my calculations are correct,
there's a 65-centimeter discrepancy.
You know what that means?
It means that in between both levels,
there's a hidden space.
And I'm gonna find it.
I'm guessing that it's a utility tunnel
for cables, for electricity,
air conditioning, that stuff.
Yeah, but they could also use that room
to smuggle cargo.
There's only one way to find out.
You had better not be thinking
about drilling a hole in the cabin floor.
- Okay?
- And why not?
Why not?
That's your problem, Cameron.
You do the opposite of what's suggested.
When you're told to go somewhere,
you don't go.
When you're told to stay at home,
you run away.
And when you cheat on your partner,
you humiliate him
and blame him for what you did.
- You are your own worst enemy.
- Yeah, well, that's your opinion.
Well, I hope, then,
that you'll understand that I'm right,
and that you'll realize it
before it's too late.
You intend to drill a hole in your cabin
in the middle of the ocean
with no means to escape.
You're assuming I'm gonna get caught.
What happens if I succeed?
You'll do as I say!
You hear me? That's an order!
Fine.
[call disconnects]
[gasps, panting]
[music subsides]
[mysterious music rises]
[exhales]
[grunts softly]
[Genoveva] I love swans.
Ever since I saw you dressed
in your white shirt, I can't stop smiling.
Dinner at 8:00 p.m., on your boat.
This is my first date
since I was 15 years old.
[chuckles softly]
Just thinking about it
gives me the chills.
I'm so excited.
- I'll escape from my babysitter.
- [chuckles]
Please don't think of me as a bonobo.
Just like you, I have the soul of a swan.
The danger is exciting.
[knocking on door]
- Uh. Yes, yes. One moment, please.
- Damián, it's Roi.
[whimsical music playing]
Out!
- Get out of here!
- Okay! I'm going.
[exhales sharply]
[whimsical music fades]
- Can I help you, handsome?
- I noticed your books.
What books?
The books about the lines in your hands,
fortune-telling, and reading palms.
Ah, reading palms.
It's a family thing.
My gran, she read palms.
So did my mother, and now I do too.
No. No, no, no.
I only do readings for strangers.
No, no way. No, no, no, no.
Come on. Do it as a personal favor.
I could do with a glimpse
into my future at this point in my life,
if you don't mind.
Go on. Please.
[clears throat]
There's no need to be nervous.
So, this one here is your line of destiny,
and this fork is not very common.
Only people blessed with luck possess it.
Yours is very pronounced.
[chuckles]
Look, here it is.
Yeah, yeah.
- And romance?
- Ah!
You wanna know?
[laughs]
Your heart line is complicated
and all tangled up.
And what does that mean?
It means lots of affairs.
Numerous. And passionate.
It's the line of a man who enjoys life.
But here, things get
much more interesting.
Now the line is more intense. Much richer.
This, this is a grand romance.
Andalusian love, I'd say. Your true love.
A beautiful, wonderful woman.
A bit of a thief
and a part-time pyromaniac.
Yours will be a beautiful love story.
What else?
What is it?
I just… read the future.
I don't change it.
But it's very positive.
Can you tell me when this is gonna happen?
Why do you wanna know that?
Let's just say
that I'm dying to experience it.
[Candela] Hm.
Tell me everything.
[inhales sharply]
[sighs]
I've got some good news and some bad news.
Maybe start with the bad.
The bad news is…
that you're going to be seriously ill.
And the good news?
The good news is, you won't die from it.
- [cell phone vibrating]
- [sighs]
Working overtime?
It's okay. Have your chat with the gang.
I'm gonna go help my father.
- [Berlin] Yes?
- We're all here. You're on speaker.
- Can you talk?
- Hm. Go ahead.
Down below in the crypt,
there's a titanium vault,
shaped like an igloo.
Behind the vault door is a corridor
that explodes like a ring of fire
if the duke's iris isn't scanned.
The vault contains deposits
of methane gas. It's highly inflammable.
Very exotic.
And you discovered this macabre
megalomaniac fantasy with the geo-radar?
No, I witnessed all of it
with my own eyes.
Last night,
I was walking around the palace,
and I ran into the duke,
who was having trouble sleeping too.
We had a few drinks,
and then he took me to see the stables.
To the stables? [scoffs]
Late at night?
And what are you insinuating, Roi?
Nothing, um… it's just that you kicked me
out of your room.
You were on all fours.
There seemed to be someone in your bed.
So when you say
you were down in the stables,
I… well, I made an association.
Yeah. And what's with the bodyguard?
'Cause I think
there's something weird going on.
Maybe the duke
would like to take him riding.
We were talking, not riding.
It was a fraternal night of male bonding.
Of camaraderie.
We embraced… a horse.
It's a meditation technique.
Good for reducing stress.
We talked about life.
About death. We sang a Mexican folk song.
Lovely. And what happened after?
He took me down to the crypt
and showed me around.
As we suspected, the first door opens
with an alphanumeric code.
But as soon as you enter the hallway,
if the system cannot identify
the duke's iris,
death by fire.
It's a masterpiece of security.
It's impenetrable.
The guy is a genius.
There's no way we can rob that vault.
Of course we're going to rob this vault!
There is always a means and a way.
Oh, yeah? Which way?
Tell me. Remove the duke's eyeballs
so we can scan them?
Well, we don't have
to remove anyone's eyeballs.
We just have to get more info.
Find other ways to get inside. That's all.
Exactly. Keila, are you thinking
what I'm thinking?
Oxygen levels?
[Keila] It's worth exploring.
With the data we have,
we can calculate the volume of oxygen
in the corridor
and the time of combustion.
- It's possible.
- [Bruce] Interesting.
Now, maybe you can explain it to us?
Hm? In simple terms?
Once the fire uses
all the oxygen in the vault,
there'll be nothing left,
and it'll burn out.
That way, we can move on
to the next phase.
Which means opening the igloo door, right?
With no oxygen to breathe?
All we need are oxygen tanks.
And a couple of fireproof suits
to survive the fire.
For God's sake, fireproof suits can only
withstand the heat for a certain time.
Sometimes only seconds.
Any miscalculation would be fatal.
We'll be extra conservative.
And how do we get past the titanium door?
Hm? In a space with no oxygen.
How will we ignite a thermal lance?
Huh? What do we do then?
We'll work it out.
Now, what the fuck is your problem?
You don't want to do this?
No. Of course I want to do it.
I'm just calculating all the risks.
Do not start lying to me now, Damián.
You're like a teenager trying to lose
his virginity with the duchess.
Exchanging messages all day,
meeting up in secret,
while at the same time becoming
best friends with her husband.
I know you.
You're beginning to feel empathy.
It's quite possible
that you're even considering
that this heist would be a betrayal.
Yes or no? What is it you say? Hmm?
All robberies require surgical precision.
So, do you still think
you're acting like a professional?
I suppose not.
Whatever we have to do, brother,
we'll find the solution with science.
Like we've always done.
[call disconnects]
Can I have the check, please?
[woman] I'll take care of that.
JUNE 23
[somber music playing]
- Camille.
- Good to see you.
I'm glad you haven't forgotten my name.
And I haven't forgotten yours either.
I have a surprise for you at my hotel.
- Come with me, please.
- No. No.
Right now is not a good time.
Why don't we sit down here?
This is not an invitation.
It's an order.
Shall we?
[Damián] I've calculated
the volume of oxygen
that can be contained
in the vault corridor.
It's 76.68 cubic meters.
If we take into account that
the estimated flow rate of methane gas
through the nozzles
is 0.2 cubic meters per second,
then, theoretically, the fire
should not last more than 45 seconds
before all the oxygen
in the corridor is consumed.
That's how long the suits last
before catching fire?
That's right.
[Keila] At ignition,
and for a few tenths of a second,
the temperature will reach
1,963 degrees Celsius.
After that,
it stabilizes between 400 and 600 degrees.
[Damián] Certain materials
can resist that kind of temperature.
Fibers like Nomex.
Or like aluminum suits
worn by firefighters.
And how exactly do we know
the suits will work?
We can run a test.
[Bruce] How?
We can use a flamethrower.
You think this is
a fucking escape room, Roi?
So after the demolition game,
set ourselves on fire?
I just want the adrenaline rush.
I'm not afraid.
We need someone that's levelheaded, Roi.
Not a kamikaze. It's Bruce.
I'm sorry? He's volunteering,
and you're asking me?
- Mm-hm.
- Newsflash, I'm not goin' in there.
- I'm telling you it's feasible.
- Inside, it's gonna be 600 degrees.
I like my beer cold.
It's not a discussion. You're both going.
Now, get outta here, and find out
where you can get those suits.
I've got my own stuff to do.
[elevator bell dings]
Here we are.
You look as beautiful as ever, Camille.
Although there's something different.
Maybe it's the gun.
You think I've changed?
Really?
[scoffs]
Maybe.
There's been
quite a few changes in my life.
My ex-husband,
with a love child, ended up incarcerated.
And there's my rather elusive lover,
who stood me up in Singapore.
[tearfully] Why didn't you come?
I found myself trapped
in the coffee triangle of Colombia
when a… volcano suddenly erupted.
And all flights were canceled.
What are you doing?
Relax.
All the roads in the country were blocked.
Travel was shut down for several days.
It was impossible to leave.
And so, in desperation,
I phoned the Blue Moon in Singapore.
And then I had this brilliant idea
while speaking with Ralph the waiter.
He agreed to help me.
To help you how?
I bought a ticket to Argentina,
and I asked him to print it out,
put it in a red envelope with your name
and with my phone number on it.
He was to hand it to you
when you arrived at the Blue Moon.
I imagined it would be romantic
to meet up on another continent
because of a volcano erupting.
After all, our relationship
was kind of volcanic.
I never got that envelope.
I definitely didn't pick up
on his intentions.
I shouldn't have been so generous
with my tip to Ralph.
And probably should've
only paid him after.
When the time for our date came
and you didn't turn up, I called again.
Blue Moon?
I'm sorry.
Ralph didn't show up for his shift.
Can't help you right now.
I insisted and called him back.
[phone rings]
But I have to admit, at that point,
I was irritated
and wasn't my usual pleasant self.
Stop calling!
[Berlin] I never heard back from Ralph.
And I never heard about the 20,000
I gave him or the red envelope.
Or you, naturally.
- [Camille sighs]
- [dramatic orchestral music playing]
We spent the same night
waiting for each other.
[sighs] On two different continents.
[somber music playing]
But now we're both here.
Together.
An erupting volcano
couldn't even keep us apart.
[music grows tense]
[Berlin sighs]
Are you really gonna make me
steal a kiss from you at gunpoint?
[Berlin sighs]
No matter how much you point that gun,
you'll never get that kiss, Camille.
Because we've missed our moment.
I'm in love with another person now.
I know that.
I know. I know because I've seen her.
That bubbly Andalusian.
So spirited, right?
But I also had
another person in my life when we met.
And all the same,
I let you into that taxi.
I let you accompany me to that concert.
I gave you the opportunity to come
into my life and change my world.
Now you owe me that same opportunity.
And that's why I came looking for you.
[knocking on door]
Don't move.
[knocking continues]
[Keila] Damián's really
on edge these days.
[Bruce] Just like us, I guess.
- What do you mean by "just like us"?
- Didn't you get what Berlin was saying?
Damián is in a love triangle
with the duke and duchess.
- Keila, can I have your phone?
- Sure.
Can you unlock it?
[sighs] Time to call that guy.
What guy?
No, no, no, no, no. Please don't.
Keila, let's handle this like grown-ups.
We're not teenagers anymore.
Do you still have him saved under "Mommy"?
- [whimsical music playing]
- Yeah.
[line ringing]
[Claudio] Hey there, Keila.
No. It's me, Bruce. Her boyfriend.
You didn't steal her phone
to spy on her, did you?
No, no, no, no, no. She's right beside me.
- Go ahead. Say hi.
- Uh. Hi, Claudio.
Keila, are you all right?
- [Keila] Yeah, I'm fine.
- [Bruce] Everybody's chill, Claudio.
We wanted to ask you something.
See if you wanted dinner?
- What do you think, man?
- Why?
Is this some kinda plan
to beat me up or something like that?
No! No, no. On the contrary.
How about we get some margaritas
and tacos?
We catch up and have some fun?
- We let loose. See what happens.
- We'll text you the location.
- See you tomorrow.
- [call ends]
I am genuinely curious to see
how this throuple thing will pan out.
[chuckles]
- [gulls calling]
- [whimsical music fades]
[tapping on window]
[mysterious music playing]
[exhales sharply]
Genoveva.
I'm sorry I didn't recognize you.
The blond hair suits you really well.
[laughs] It's a wig
that I used to throw off Samuel.
I went in the front door to Zara's.
I put on the wig and left the other way.
- Like a double agent.
- [both laugh]
The adrenaline!
Uh. Oh, I'm so sorry.
Please come in. Please. Hm.
[Damián sighs]
How wonderful, living on a boat.
[chuckles] I guess.
[Genoveva chuckles]
You have no idea how happy I was
when you put on that white shirt.
[chuckles] Um, well, to be honest,
I didn't have much of a choice, really.
You had the upper hand.
I mean, an obligatory dress code.
Are you saying
that you're here because I made you?
Mm. No, no, no, no.
[scoffs] This is
the price we agreed on for the date.
500,000.
In photocopies.
You're more devious than I am.
However,
there's something I just don't get.
If you already have all the cash,
and it appears that I've forced you
to meet me here,
then why this amazing meal?
With candles and flowers.
What are you doing?
Huh? What are you doing?!
Do you find it amusing that I have
to disguise myself in the changing room?
- No, that's not it at all.
- That's not it? So what is it?
Why have you gone this far?
The thrill of being with a married woman?
No. I'm not toying with you.
I've fallen in love with you.
During the day, I avoid you,
and at night, I fantasize about you.
And yesterday,
I even kept all of your Post-its.
I'm living in torment.
I dream about you constantly.
The other night, I dreamt of you.
We were on a boat together,
just like this one.
Would you like to know what happened?
No. No. 'Cause nothing can happen.
Nothing at all.
The first time I rejected you
because I work for your husband.
Now I have two more reasons.
And the first reason is because…
the duke and I, over the past few days,
have started to become friends.
I'm sure you can appreciate why.
Your husband's a good man.
And the second reason?
My marriage ended because of infidelity.
I know how it can destroy people's lives.
And I told myself…
I'd never do that to anyone.
The things you talk about…
Infidelity and… betrayal,
all these terrible things that overshadow
a moment that could be
truly beautiful for us.
Then again,
I suppose it's not cheating
if I touch your hand.
I suppose you're right.
And I suppose
it's not a sin
if I caress your arm.
I suppose not, no.
[gently] Then
it can't be
a sin
to smell the perfume on your neck.
[inhales deeply]
[softly] I suppose not.
[sighs]
I suppose, then, it won't be a sin
if we both begin dancing cheek to cheek.
I suppose not.
[tender music rises]
- ["At Last" by Etta James playing]
- ♪ At last ♪
♪ My love has come along ♪
♪ My lonely days are over ♪
♪ And life is like a song ♪
♪ Oh, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ At last ♪
♪ The skies above ♪
[romantic tune fades]
[tense music rises]
[both breathing shakily]
I have… I have a proposition for you.
Let's go somewhere. Let's run away.
We can wait until all this is finished.
And I promise you
that once this job is completed,
and once you leave your husband,
we can go anywhere
in the world that you want.
We can live anywhere.
We can dance anywhere.
Thank you for the generous offer.
I'll let you know my decision.
- [song resumes]
- ♪ At last ♪
[door closes]
[romantic song ends]
[somber violin music playing]
What's going on, Camille? Tell me.
Just café au lait.
Don't you remember?
This is how it all began.
Sitting at the bar in that café.
The smell of fresh croissants,
nice and hot.
The taste of Paris… on your lips.
[birds singing]
[Berlin and Camille's laughter echoes]
Is it coming back to you now?
[majestic string music rises]
You heard me perform
at the club the previous night.
You heard me singing.
[performing "L'amour" in French]
[whispering lyrics]
["L'amour" building]
These panties, I took them off
when we were at the restaurant.
They're yours now.
[sultry French song fades]
[wistful piano music playing]
You can't possibly have forgotten
what we were.
What we had, what we could be.
It's not over.
Everything that we had together
is very much alive.
It's still there,
somewhere in your memories.
- [elevator bell rings]
- [Spanish guitar music playing]
I'm so sorry.
[music dies down]
[intense music playing]
I was just talking about you.
You need to shut up.
[inhales sharply] What's your name?
Camille. Pleased to meet you.
Candela.
This is the woman
I fell in love with in Paris.
Before you and I met.
Why start something with me if everything
was so good in Paris with her?
Because… I was no longer with her.
- Ah.
- [Berlin] It's true.
When I first met you,
we were no longer together.
We hadn't been together
for over two months,
since I missed her
at the Blue Moon in Singapore.
[Camille] I never heard from him again.
Love stories come to an end
when people break up, when they separate.
In this case,
however, neither of us broke up.
Camille, uh, our relationship
was a game of telephone.
Of missed opportunities
on different continents
that ultimately failed.
I'm crazy about you.
I've never loved anyone like this.
But I don't belong with you,
and you don't belong with me.
And this has nothing to do with her.
I'm sure she's wonderful.
Our lives are too different.
I've never had a date
at the Blue Moon in Singapore.
I don't even know what that is,
and I don't care.
But you do.
You care about things that are shiny
and elegant and sophisticated.
And me, I care about seeing my family,
sharing a moment with friends,
stuffing my face,
eating fried eggs with my fingers,
helping my dad pick watermelons
on Fridays.
I find beauty in small things.
You see, my life is simple.
And I love my life
because it's the only one I've got.
But you've had 50 lives.
And, in each of these lives,
you have champagne on ice.
[Berlin sighs]
Out of these 50 lives,
I choose this one to spend with you.
This is the life that I want.
Isn't it amazing what we've gone through?
You know what else?
Our love would have lasted forever.
- But we can't be together.
- Why not?
Because our love has an expiration date,
and I prefer to leave right now.
And if you have any respect
for what we had,
don't you ever come looking for me.
So long.
Ciao, Camille.
[dramatic music swells]
[breathing shakily]
[footsteps above]
[suspenseful music playing]
♪ I want to move with your body… ♪
[electronic music continues indistinctly]
[suspenseful music intensifies]
Each of us will carry two guns.
And two magazines.
Things might get messy.
How many?
There's gonna be at least eight of them.
Four in each vehicle.
[Roi] The suits will be in the back.
We have to be quick.
[Damián, muffled] The sooner you get out,
the better.
[Bruce] Yeah.
We'll go to the meeting point.
Once you've got the suits, let me know.
I've gotta go somewhere.
I'll stay here. I have to find a way
to open that igloo before it's too late.
This one's a smash and grab, okay?
Make it quick and smooth.
[energetic music playing]
[siren wailing]
Go, go, go, go!
There's someone inside!
Pull!
[energetic music fades]
[engine starts]
[siren wailing]
[gritty rock music playing]
[Bruce chuckles]
[rock music ends]
[tense music rises]
What do you want? I told you to stay away.
Is this how you show your respect for me?
No, stay where you are.
She's asking you to leave.
Please hear me out, and after that,
if you still want me to leave, I'll leave.
Hey. Help me get something in the trailer.
[music intensifies]
Leave, asshole.
We know you were with that French woman.
Yesterday nothing happened with Camille.
What really happened was
that you saw an opportunity to escape
and run away from me.
I'm tired. I don't want to talk anymore.
Candela, if for one moment,
you believed that I was cheating on you,
you would've sprayed gasoline
all over me and set me on fire.
You just panicked and ran away.
And you hang on to a champagne bottle
as an excuse to say we're different.
But you're just afraid of falling in love.
Afraid of… loving me too much.
- [Berlin] And you know what?
- What?
I've got some good news for you.
I love you just as much.
Maybe even more.
It's my destiny, right?
You told me so yourself.
But this bit here,
the bit you're worried about, who knows?
Maybe you just made a mistake.
[melancholic violin music playing]
You said we're too different.
Let me say… let me say it loud and clear
so that everyone can hear me!
For me, this is an honor…
a true honor, to come down
to this field to pick watermelons
or anything else with your family.
[music intensifies]
You better leave right now, mister,
or you'll be outta here feet first.
I'm gonna count to three.
- One!
- Dad, give me a moment.
Two!
I'm not leaving.
But there's no way
I'm gonna let this conversation
turn into a bloody tragedy.
Simón, put down the guns.
My name's not Simón.
[intense music dies down]
My name is Andrés de Fonollosa.
Usually, I live in Madrid
in the area of Barrio de Las Letras,
above a small café, the Buenos Aires.
When I was young, I was married,
and I have a son called Rafael.
And I'm a professional thief.
And the only thing that's been going
through my head since you left is,
how can I demonstrate
how crazy I am about you?
Nothing is going to stop me
from being with you.
And I want you to understand,
no matter what happens to me,
you can trust me.
The only way I found to express this…
the only way I found to convince you is…
with this.
If you don't mind, Candela,
please look inside my pocket.
I know that this might be unexpected,
but you need to decide.
Yes or… or no?
[sighs]
Yes, of course.
[triumphant music playing]
- [sighs]
- [music fades]
["Ace & Eights"
by Cavendish Music playing]
[bluesy rock fades]